Guide to the Harry Randall: Fifteenth International Brigade Films and Photographs ALBA.PHOTO.011
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series E: Miscellaneous, 1938-01-1939-09; 9594
  - Photo Unit #: E1059 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, the winner!, Jul 18, 1938; 9875 (Item 11-1573)
  - Photo Unit #: E1060 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, Mike Pappas [Michael Papadopullo], Jul 18, 1938; 9874 (Item 11-1574)
  - Photo Unit #: E1061 Shot-put contest at Lincoln-Washington fiesta, Mar 1938; 9873 (Item 11-0100)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/43)
  - Photo Unit #: E1063 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, Jul 19, 1938; 9872 (Item 11-1575)
  - Photo Unit #: E1064 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, foot race, Jul 19, 1938; 9871 (Item 11-1576)
  - Photo Unit #: E1065 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, three legged race, Jul 19, 1938; 9870 (Item 11-1577)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/50)
  - Photo Unit #: E1066 Lincoln-Washington fiesta, Jul 19, 1938; 9869 (Item 11-0101)
  - Photo Unit #: E1067 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, "Virginia item", Jul 19, 1938; 9868 (Item 11-1578)
  - Photo Unit #: E1068 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, Jul 19, 1938; 9867 (Item 11-1579)
  - Photo Unit #: E1069 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, Jul 19, 1938; 9866 (Item 11-1580)
  - Photo Unit #: E1070 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, Jul 1938; 9865 (Item 11-1581)
  - Photo Unit #: E1072 Marching to Brigade assembly (Lincoln-Washington Battalion), Jul 19, 1938; 9864 (Item 11-1582)
  - Photo Unit #: E1073 Marching to Brigade assembly (Lincoln-Washington Battalion), Jul 19, 1938; 9863 (Item 11-1583)
  - Photo Unit #: E1074 Marching to Brigade assembly (Lincoln-Washington Battalion), Jul 19, 1938; 9862 (Item 11-1584)
  - Photo Unit #: E1075 Marching to Brigade assembly (Lincoln-Washington Battalion), Jul 19, 1938; 9861 (Item 11-1585)
  - Photo Unit #: E1077 Marching to Brigade assembly (Lincoln-Washington Battalion), Jul 19, 1938; 9860 (Item 11-1586)
  - Photo Unit #: E1080 15th International Brigade Assembly, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, [marching in ranks], Jul 19, 1938; 9859 (Item 11-1785)
    (Moscow Number: 5/181/28)
  - Photo Unit #: E1081 15th International Brigade Assembly, Jul 19, 1938; 9858 (Item 11-1587)
    (Moscow Number: 5/181/26)
  - Photo Unit #: E1083 Brigade Assembly, Major José Antonio Valledor speaking, Jul 19, 1938; 9857 (Item 11-1588)
  - Photo Unit #: E1084 Brigade Assembly, Major José Antonio Valledor speaking, Jul 19, 1938; 9856 (Item 11-1589)
    (Moscow Number: 5/181/25)
  - Photo Unit #: E1085 Brigade Assembly, Major José Antonio Valledor speaking, Jul 19, 1938; 9855 (Item 11-1590)
  - Photo Unit #: E1086 15th International Brigade Assembly, 2nd anniversary of outbreak of war, Jul 19, 1938; 9854 (Item 11-1591)
  - Photo Unit #: E1087 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Marca, Jul 1938; 9853 (Item 11-0512)
  - Photo Unit #: E1089 Lincoln-Washington Battalion building a foxhole, Marca, Jul 1938; 9852 (Item 11-1204)
  - Photo Unit #: E1091 Luigi Gallo, John Gates, André Marty, Jul 1938; 9851 (Item 11-1592)
  - Photo Unit #: E1092 Chabolas [shelters] at Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Jul 1938; 9850 (Item 11-1593)
  - Photo Unit #: E1096 Members of special Machine-Gunner Battalion of 15th army corps, Jul 1938; 9849 (Item 11-1594)
  - Photo Unit #: E1100 Town square, Asco, Jul 1938; 9848 (Item 11-1595)
  - Photo Unit #: E1102 Fascist prisoners, Asco, Jul 1938; 9847 (Item 11-1596)
  - Photo Unit #: E1105 Going to the front lines, Lincoln-Washington, Jul 1938; 9846 (Item 11-0102)
  - Photo Unit #: E1107 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Jul 1938; 9845 (Item 11-0103)
  - Photo Unit #: E1108 Lincoln-Washington Battalion first-aid post, Corbera, Jul 1938; 9844 (Item 11-1597)
  - Photo Unit #: E1109 Lincoln-Washington Battalion first-aid post, Corbera, Jul 1938; 9843 (Item 11-1598)
  - Photo Unit #: E1111 Lincoln-Washington Battalion first-aid post, Corbera, Jul 1938; 9842 (Item 11-1599)
  - Photo Unit #: E1112 59th Battalion stretcher bearers at Gandesa, Jul 1938; 9841 (Item 11-1600)
    (Moscow Number: 5/186/8)
  - Photo Unit #: E1113 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Jul 1938; 9840 (Item 11-0104)
  - Photo Unit #: E1114 Lincoln-Washington Battalion observer, Corbera, Jul 1938; 9839 (Item 11-1601)
  - Photo Unit #: E1115 Lincoln-Washington Battalion observer, Corbera, 304908 (Item 11-1868)
  - Photo Unit #: E1116 Lincoln-Washington Battalion observer, Corbera, Jul 1938; 9838 (Item 11-1602)
  - Photo Unit #: E1117 Lincoln-Washington Battalion Machine-Gunner nest, Corbera, Jul 1938; 9837 (Item 11-1603)
  - Photo Unit #: E1118 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938; 9836 (Item 11-1604)
  - Photo Unit #: E1120 Battalion Captain Milton Wolff, Lincoln-Washington, Jul 1938; 9835 (Item 11-0105)
  - Photo Unit #: E1121 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Joseph Brandt, Corbera, Jul 1938; 9834 (Item 11-1605)
  - Photo Unit #: E1122 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938; 9833 (Item 11-1606)
  - Photo Unit #: E1123 Lincoln-Washington Battalion members resting, Corbera, Jul 1938; 9832 (Item 11-1607)
  - Photo Unit #: E1124 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938; 9831 (Item 11-1608)
  - Photo Unit #: E1126 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938; 9830 (Item 11-1609)
  - Photo Unit #: E1127 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938; 9829 (Item 11-1610)
  - Photo Unit #: E1128 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938; 9828 (Item 11-1611)
  - Photo Unit #: E1129 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938; 9827 (Item 11-1612)
  - Photo Unit #: E1130 [Soldiers firing rifles], Jul 1938; 9826 (Item 11-1205)
  - Photo Unit #: E1131 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938; 9825 (Item 11-1613)
  - Photo Unit #: E1132 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938; 9824 (Item 11-1614)
  - Photo Unit #: E1133 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938; 9823 (Item 11-1615)
  - Photo Unit #: E1134 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938; 9822 (Item 11-1616)
  - Photo Unit #: E1135 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938; 9821 (Item 11-1617)
  - Photo Unit #: E1136 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938; 9820 (Item 11-1618)
  - Photo Unit #: E1137 Lincoln-Washington Battalion Lieutenant Aaron Lopoff and Lieutenant Rico Rusciano, Corbera, Jul 1938; 9819 (Item 11-1619)
  - Photo Unit #: E1138 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938; 9818 (Item 11-1620)
  - Photo Unit #: E1139 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938; 9817 (Item 11-1621)
  - Photo Unit #: E1140 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938; 9816 (Item 11-1622)
  - Photo Unit #: E1141 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera [soldier, from back], undated; 9815 (Item 11-1623)
  - Photo Unit #: E1142 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938; 9814 (Item 11-1624)
  - Photo Unit #: E1143 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938; 9813 (Item 11-1625)
  - Photo Unit #: E1144 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera [soldier, on ground], Jul 1938; 9812 (Item 11-1626)
  - Photo Unit #: E1145 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera [machine gun], Jul 1938; 9811 (Item 11-1627)
  - Photo Unit #: E1146 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938; 9810 (Item 11-1628)
  - Photo Unit #: E1147 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938; 9809 (Item 11-1629)
  - Photo Unit #: E1148 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938; 9808 (Item 11-1630)
  - Photo Unit #: E1149 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938; 9807 (Item 11-1631)
  - Photo Unit #: E1150 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938; 9806 (Item 11-1632)
  - Photo Unit #: E1151 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, machine-gun nest, Gandesa [5 soldiers], Jul 1938; 9805 (Item 11-1633)
  - Photo Unit #: E1152 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, machine-gun nest, Gandesa, Jul 1938; 9804 (Item 11-1634)
  - Photo Unit #: E1153 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, machine-gun nest, Gandesa [4 soldiers], Jul 1938; 9803 (Item 11-1635)
  - Photo Unit #: E1154 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, [7 soldiers,] Gandesa, Jul 1938; 9802 (Item 11-1636)
  - Photo Unit #: E1155 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, [soldier using] telephone, machine-gun company, Gandesa, Jul 1938; 9801 (Item 11-1637)
  - Photo Unit #: E1156 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, [two machine-gunners in trench], undated; 9800 (Item 11-1638)
  - Photo Unit #: E1157 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, machine-gun company, Gandesa [soldiers at gun], Jul 1938; 9799 (Item 11-1639)
  - Photo Unit #: E1158 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, machine-gun company, Gandesa [2 soldiers at gun], Jul 1938; 9798 (Item 11-1640)
  - Photo Unit #: E1159 Lincoln-Washington Battalion Estado Mayor, Headquarters of 59th Battalion, 15th International Brigade, during attack on Gandesa, Mark Millman, Aug 1938; 9797 (Item 11-1641)
  - Photo Unit #: E1160 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Gandesa [soldiers walking up hill], Jul 1938; 9796 (Item 11-1642)
  - Photo Unit #: E1161 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, stretcher bearers, Gandesa, Jul 1938; 9795 (Item 11-1643)
  - Photo Unit #: E1162 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Gandesa [soldiers and horses on trail], Jul 1938; 9794 (Item 11-1644)
  - Photo Unit #: E1163 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Gandesa [soldiers and horses on trail], Jul 1938; 9793 (Item 11-1645)
  - Photo Unit #: E1164 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Gandesa [4 solderis, one with bandaged head, on trail], Jul 1938; 9792 (Item 11-1646)
  - Photo Unit #: E1165 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, stretcher bearers, Gandesa, Jul 1938; 9791 (Item 11-1647)
  - Photo Unit #: E1166 Lincoln-Washington Battalion stretcher-bearers, Gandesa, Aug 1938; 9790 (Item 11-1648)
  - Photo Unit #: E1167 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Gandesa [soldiers relaxing on ground], Jul 1938; 9789 (Item 11-1649)
  - Photo Unit #: E1168 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Gandesa [trench?], Jul 1938; 9788 (Item 11-1650)
  - Photo Unit #: E1169 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Gandesa, Jul 1938; 9787 (Item 11-1651)
  - Photo Unit #: E1170 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Gandesa [soldiers on ground], Jul 1938; 9786 (Item 11-1652)
  - Photo Unit #: E1171 Looking toward Corbera [landscape, long view], Jul 1938; 9785 (Item 11-1653)
  - Photo Unit #: E1172 Looking toward Gandesa [landscape, long view], Jul 1938; 9784 (Item 11-1654)
  - Photo Unit #: E1173 59th Battalion, trench mortar, Gandesa, Jul 1938; 9783 (Item 11-1655)
  - Photo Unit #: E1174 59th Battalion, machine-gun nest, Gandesa, Jul 1938; 9782 (Item 11-1656)
  - Photo Unit #: E1175 59th Battalion, Gandesa [soldier with rifle, in trench?], Jul 1938; 9781 (Item 11-1657)
  - Photo Unit #: E1176 59th Battalion, Gandesa [soldier aiming rifle, behind rocks], Jul 1938; 9780 (Item 11-1658)
  - Photo Unit #: E1177 59th Battalion, water detail, Gandesa [two soldiers, with tins], Jul 1938; 9779 (Item 11-1659)
  - Photo Unit #: E1178 59th Battalion, water detail, Gandesa [one soldier], Jul 1938; 9778 (Item 11-1660)
  - Photo Unit #: E1179 59th Battalion, evacuating wounded, Gandesa [soldier on stretcher], Jul 1938; 9777 (Item 11-1661)
  - Photo Unit #: E1180 59th Battalion, evacuating wounded, Gandesa [soldier on stretcher], Jul 1938; 9776 (Item 11-1662)
  - Photo Unit #: E1181 15th International Brigade Sanidad [Health] post, Gandesa, Aug 1938; 9775 (Item 11-1663)
  - Photo Unit #: E1182 Lincoln-Washington Armory, Gandesa, Aug 1938; 9774 (Item 11-1664)
  - Photo Unit #: E1183 15th International Brigade, Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Gandesa [men at tunnle, or bridge, entrance], Aug 1938; 9773 (Item 11-1665)
  - Photo Unit #: E1184 Observer, Gandesa, Aug 1938; 9772 (Item 11-1666)
  - Photo Unit #: E1185 Planes overhead, Aug 1938; 9771 (Item 11-1667)
  - Photo Unit #: E1186 Major José Antonio Valledor and Lieutenant [?] Julia, Gandesa, Aug 1938; 9770 (Item 11-1668)
  - Photo Unit #: E1187 Major José Antonio Valledor and Lieutenant Julia, Gandesa, Aug 1938; 9769 (Item 11-1669)
  - Photo Unit #: E1188 Captain Dunbar and Major José Antonio Valledor, Gandesa [with 2 others], Aug 1938; 9768 (Item 11-1670)
  - Photo Unit #: E1189 Captain Dunbar and Major José Antonio Valledor, Gandesa [with two others], Aug 1938; 9767 (Item 11-1671)
  - Photo Unit #: E1190 Captain Rollin Dart, Gandesa, Aug 1938; 9766 (Item 11-1672)
  - Photo Unit #: E1191 Morris Stamm and John Coon, Lincoln-Washington, Gandesa, Aug 1938; 9765 (Item 11-1673)
    Available Formats: Original Negative; Copy Negative; Print
  - Photo Unit #: E1192 Loading a machine-gun belt, Gandesa [2 soldiers], Aug 1938; 9764 (Item 11-1674)
  - Photo Unit #: E1193 Patrick Roosevelt and Pete [?], with machine gun, Gandesa, Lincoln-Washington, Aug 1938; 9763 (Item 11-1675)
  - Photo Unit #: E1194 Abraham Copeland of Transmiciones [Transmissions], Gandesa, Aug 1938; 9762 (Item 11-1676)
  - Photo Unit #: E1195 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Gandesa, Aug 1938; 9761 (Item 11-1677)
  - Photo Unit #: E1196 Lincoln-Washington Battalion David (Red) Drummond, Nick Pappas, Eluard Luchell McDaniels, Gandesa, Aug 1938; 9760 (Item 11-1678)
  - Photo Unit #: E1197 Captured Machine-Gunner, Lincoln-Washington Battalion Gandesa, Aug 1938; 9759 (Item 11-1679)
  - Photo Unit #: E1198 Sergeant Guy Thorpe and Sergeant Max Bowers, Aug 1938; 9758 (Item 11-1680)
  - Photo Unit #: E1200 Cabo Narciso Gonzales, Adjuntant Lieutenant Jack Cooper, Jefe, Rafael Maltes, Commissar, Spanish M. E. [?] Company, Gandesa, Aug 1938; 9757 (Item 11-1681)
  - Photo Unit #: E1201 Herman (Gabby) Klein sleeping, Lincoln-Washington Company 3, Gandesa, Aug 1938; 9756 (Item 11-0106)
  - Photo Unit #: E1203 David Lipton firing rifle, Lincoln-Washington, Company 3, Gandesa, Aug 1938; 9755 (Item 11-1682)
  - Photo Unit #: E1204 Lincoln-Washington Battalion Company 3, Gandesa, Aug 1938; 9754 (Item 11-1683)
  - Photo Unit #: E1206 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion Company 3, Gandesa, Aug 1938; 9753 (Item 11-1684)
  - Photo Unit #: E1207 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Gandesa, Aug 1938; 9752 (Item 11-1685)
  - Photo Unit #: E1209 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Gandesa, Aug 1939; 9751 (Item 11-1686)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/14)
  - Photo Unit #: E1210 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Gandesa, Aug 1938; 9750 (Item 11-1687)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/55)
  - Photo Unit #: E1237 Water tank, Corbera, Aug 1938; 9749 (Item 11-1688)
  - Photo Unit #: E1240 Cubans, Corbera, Aug 1938; 9748 (Item 11-1689)
  - Photo Unit #: E1241 Cubans, Corbera, Aug 1938; 9747 (Item 11-1690)
  - Photo Unit #: E1242 Sandor Voros, Miles Tomalin, Ernest Mahoney, Corbera, Aug 1938; 9746 (Item 11-1691)
  - Photo Unit #: E1244 Lincoln-Washington group, Aug 1938; 9745 (Item 11-0107)
  - Photo Unit #: E1245 Alvah Bessie and Edwin Rolfe, Lincoln-Washington, Aug 1938; 9744 (Item 11-0108)
  - Photo Unit #: E1246 Aaron Lopoff, Alvah Bessie, Rico Rusciano at Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Aug 1938; 9743 (Item 11-1692)
  - Photo Unit #: E1247 Ernst Toller and David Roosevelt, Corbera, Aug 1938; 9742 (Item 11-1693)
  - Photo Unit #: E1248 Ernst Toller and David Roosevelt, Corbera, Aug 1938; 9741 (Item 11-1694)
  - Photo Unit #: E1249 Ernst Toller, Aug 1938; 9740 (Item 11-0109)
  - Photo Unit #: E1250 Lincoln-Washington group playing cards, Corbera, Aug 1938; 9739 (Item 11-1695)
  - Photo Unit #: E1251 Lincoln-Washington observers, Corbera, Aug 1938; 9738 (Item 11-1696)
  - Photo Unit #: E1252 Lincoln-Washington positions at rest, Corbera, Aug 1938; 9737 (Item 11-1697)
  - Photo Unit #: E1257 Tony Pujol digging refugio, Aug 1938; 9736 (Item 11-0110)
  - Photo Unit #: E1258 David Gordon, Maurice Miller, Edwin Rolfe, Corbera, Aug 1938; 9735 (Item 11-0513)
  - Photo Unit #: E1259 Estado Mayor [Headquarters] group, runners, etc., Corbera, Aug 1938; 9734 (Item 11-0514)
  - Photo Unit #: E1260 Estado Mayor [Headquarters] group, Thomas Norton in center, Corbera, Aug 1938; 9733 (Item 11-0515)
  - Photo Unit #: E1262 Group from Williamsburg, New York, Lincoln-Washington, Corbera, Aug 1938; 9732 (Item 11-1698)
  - Photo Unit #: E1265 MacKenzie-Papineau Company, 5 citiations: Deszo Beke, Jose Asenci, Yaigve Lekto, Toivo Suni, undated; 9731 (Item 11-1699)
  - Photo Unit #: E1268 59th Battalion, Company 2, citations: Luis Peraza, Lieutenant Geronimo Lopez, Pedro Aquilla Rio, Corbera, Aug 1938; 9730 (Item 11-0516)
  - Photo Unit #: E1276 Salvador Plana, James Bourne, William Griffiths, Mora de Ebro, Aug 1938; 9729 (Item 11-0517)
  - Photo Unit #: E1278 Some of the Commissariat, Mora de Ebro, Aug 1938; 9728 (Item 11-0518)
  - Photo Unit #: E1283 Waiting to cross the Ebro, Jul 25, 1938; 9727 (Item 11-0519)
  - Photo Unit #: E1285 Building foot bridge across Ebro, Jul 25, 1938; 9726 (Item 11-0520)
  - Photo Unit #: E1286 Building foot bridge across Ebro, Jul 25, 1938; 9725 (Item 11-0521)
  - Photo Unit #: E1287 Building foot bridge across Ebro [carrying lumber], June 25, 1938; 304909 (Item 11-1869)
  - Photo Unit #: E1288 Building foot bridge across Ebro [sections of bridge piled on river bank], 304910 (Item 11-1870)
  - Photo Unit #: E1289 Building foot bridge across Ebro, Jul 25, 1938; 9724 (Item 11-0522)
  - Photo Unit #: E1292 Stretching the cable across Ebro, Jul 25, 1938; 9723 (Item 11-0523)
  - Photo Unit #: E1293 Stretching the cable across Ebro, Jul 25, 1938; 9722 (Item 11-0524)
  - Photo Unit #: E1302 Building the foot bridge, Jul 25, 1938; 9721 (Item 11-1700)
  - Photo Unit #: E1303 Stretching the cable across Ebro, Jul 25, 1938; 9720 (Item 11-0525)
  - Photo Unit #: E1305 Building the foot bridge, Jul 25, 1938; 9719 (Item 11-0526)
  - Photo Unit #: E1306 Crossing the Ebro [placing the lines], 304911 (Item 11-1877)
  - Photo Unit #: E1307 Building the foot bridge, Jul 25, 1938; 9718 (Item 11-0527)
  - Photo Unit #: E1308 Building foot bridge across Ebro, Jul 1938; 9717 (Item 11-1206)
  - Photo Unit #: E1309 Building the foot bridge, Jul 25, 1938; 9716 (Item 11-0528)
  - Photo Unit #: E1312 Crossing Ebro by boat and bridge, Jul 1938; 9715 (Item 11-1207)
  - Photo Unit #: E1313 Crossing the Ebro by boat and bridge, Jul 25, 1938; 9714 (Item 11-1701)
  - Photo Unit #: E1315 Crossing the Ebro by boat and bridge [landing in a boat], 304912 (Item 11-1876)
  - Photo Unit #: E1317 Crossing the Ebro by boat and bridge, Jul 25, 1938; 9713 (Item 11-1702)
  - Photo Unit #: E1318 Crossing the Ebro by boat and bridge [men walking to boats], 304913 (Item 11-1871)
  - Photo Unit #: E1320 Crossing the Ebro by boat and bridge[launching a boat, another in background], 304914 (Item 11-1872)
  - Photo Unit #: E1321 Crossing the Ebro by boat and bridge, Jul 25, 1938; 9712 (Item 11-0529)
  - Photo Unit #: E1322 Crossing the Ebro by boat and bridge, Jul 1938; 9711 (Item 11-1703)
  - Photo Unit #: E1323 Crossing the Ebro by boat and bridge, Jul 25, 1938; 9710 (Item 11-0530)
  - Photo Unit #: E1325 Crossing Ebro by boat and bridge, Jul 1938; 9709 (Item 11-0531)
  - Photo Unit #: E1328 Crossing Ebro by boat and bridge, Jul 1938; 9708 (Item 11-0532)
  - Photo Unit #: E1333 Crossing Ebro by boat and bridge, Jul 1938; 9707 (Item 11-0533)
  - Photo Unit #: E1336 Crossing the Ebro by boat and bridge[launching a boat, close-up view], 304915 (Item 11-1873)
  - Photo Unit #: E1338 Crossing the Ebro by pontoon bridge, 304916 (Item 11-1874)
  - Photo Unit #: E1340 William Allander and his truck after bombing, Jul 1938; 9706 (Item 11-0534)
  - Photo Unit #: E1341 Bill Allander and his truck after bombing [with man unloading a box], undated; 9705 (Item 11-1704)
  - Photo Unit #: E1344 Captured rifles, Jul 1938; 9704 (Item 11-0535)
  - Photo Unit #: E1349 Corbera recaptured, Aug 1938; 9703 (Item 11-0536)
  - Photo Unit #: E1350 Brigade Estado Mayor [Headquarters], undated; 9702 (Item 11-0537)
  - Photo Unit #: E1354 Shelling near Lincoln-Washington positions, undated; 9701 (Item 11-0538)
  - Photo Unit #: E1355 Shelling near Lincoln-Washington positions, undated; 9700 (Item 11-0539)
  - Photo Unit #: E1358 Unexploded Shell, undated; 9699 (Item 11-0540)
  - Photo Unit #: E1359 Drawing water at MacKenzie-Papineau [?] [donkey with several soldiers], undated; 9698 (Item 11-1705)
  - Photo Unit #: E1361 Lincoln-Washington Battalion out for rest, undated; 9697 (Item 11-0541)
  - Photo Unit #: E1362 Heliograf squad [3 men], Jul 1938; 9696 (Item 11-1706)
  - Photo Unit #: E1363 Heliograf squad, Jul 1938; 9695 (Item 11-1208)
  - Photo Unit #: E1365 Heliograph squad, Russell Stephens [3 men w/equipement], Jul 1938; 9694 (Item 11-1707)
  - Photo Unit #: E1367 Heliograf squad, Jul 1938; 9693 (Item 11-0542)
  - Photo Unit #: E1368 Doctor Julius Hene, Major Edward Cecil [?] Smith, Hamish Frazer, undated; 9692 (Item 11-1708)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/43)
  - Photo Unit #: E1371 Brigade Estado Mayor [Headquarters], undated; 9691 (Item 11-0543)
  - Photo Unit #: E1372 Washing up, undated; 9690 (Item 11-0544)
  - Photo Unit #: E1374 William Van Felix and Ernest Amatniek, undated; 9689 (Item 11-0545)
  - Photo Unit #: E1375 Lincoln-Washington wounded, undated; 9688 (Item 11-0546)
  - Photo Unit #: E1376 Lincoln-Washington wounded, undated; 9687 (Item 11-0547)
  - Photo Unit #: E1377 Lincoln-Washington wounded, undated; 9686 (Item 11-0548)
  - Photo Unit #: E1378 Lincoln-Washington wounded, undated; 9685 (Item 11-0549)
  - Photo Unit #: E1379 Lincoln-Washington wounded, undated; 9684 (Item 11-0550)
  - Photo Unit #: E1380 Lincoln-Washington wounded, undated; 9683 (Item 11-0551)
  - Photo Unit #: E1383 Loading machine-gun belts, undated; 9682 (Item 11-1209)
  - Photo Unit #: E1384 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, undated; 9681 (Item 11-0552)
  - Photo Unit #: E1386 Lincoln-Washington Estado Mayor [Headquarters], undated; 9680 (Item 11-0553)
  - Photo Unit #: E1387 Lincoln-Washington Estado Mayor [Headquarters], George Watt and Major Milton Wolff, with others, at Gandesa Front, Aug 1938; 9679 (Item 11-1709)
  - Photo Unit #: E1395 Brigade Sanidad [Health], undated; 9678 (Item 11-0554)
  - Photo Unit #: E1399 Brigade Sanidad [Health], undated; 9677 (Item 11-0555)
  - Photo Unit #: E1401 Brigade Estado Mayor [Headquarters], undated; 9676 (Item 11-0556)
  - Photo Unit #: E1402 John Gates, undated; 9675 (Item 11-1210)
  - Photo Unit #: E1405 Volunteer Shaving [another], 304917 (Item 11-1878)
  - Photo Unit #: E1407 Brigade Topographers, undated; 9674 (Item 11-0557)
  - Photo Unit #: E1408 Brigade Topographers, undated; 9673 (Item 11-0558)
  - Photo Unit #: E1412 Fascist prisoners, Aug 1938; 9672 (Item 11-0559)
  - Photo Unit #: E1414 Fascist prisoners, undated; 9671 (Item 11-1710)
  - Photo Unit #: E1415 Fascist prisoners, undated; 9670 (Item 11-0560)
  - Photo Unit #: E1417 Fascist prisoners, undated; 9669 (Item 11-0561)
  - Photo Unit #: E1423 15 International Brigade Estado Mayor [Headquarters], undated; 9668 (Item 11-0562)
  - Photo Unit #: E1428 Lincoln-Washington Estado Mayor [Headquarters], undated; 9667 (Item 11-0563)
  - Photo Unit #: E1429 Lincoln-Washington Estado Mayor [Headquarters], undated; 9666 (Item 11-0564)
  - Photo Unit #: E1430 Lincoln-Washington Transmiciones [Transmissions], undated; 9665 (Item 11-0565)
  - Photo Unit #: E1434 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, group photograph, Sep 1938; 9664 (Item 11-1847)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/50)
  - Photo Unit #: E1436 Soldier, reading mail, undated; 9663 (Item 11-1211)
  - Photo Unit #: E1439 School kids and James Bourne, undated; 9662 (Item 11-0566)
  - Photo Unit #: E1440 MacKenzie-Papineau, Edward Cecil Smith [playing checkers], Jul 1938; 9661 (Item 11-1711)
  - Photo Unit #: E1442 Building cave room at Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Sierra Pandols, Aug 1938; 9660 (Item 11-1712)
  - Photo Unit #: E1445 Estado Mayor [Headquarters] Position, Sierra Pandols, Aug 1938; 9659 (Item 11-1713)
  - Photo Unit #: E1446 Headquarters, Sierra Pandols, undated; 9658 (Item 11-1714)
    (Moscow Number: 5/191/89)